<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Translation on Toha</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/translation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Translation on Toha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:20:50 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/translation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>How to add an unsupported language</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/translation/new-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:20:50 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/translation/new-language/</guid>
      <description>If you want to translate to an unsupported language, you can translate the UI elements.
Create an i18n file To do so, you have to create the i18n diretory inside the root of the site, the directory where you can find the config.yaml file, and directories like data, content, etc.
Afterwards, you can create the file &amp;lt;language_code&amp;gt;.toml into the i18n directory. In this directory, you can find all language codes with the flag that will appear with that code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Translate Posts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/translation/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:20:50 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/translation/content/</guid>
      <description>This theme has built-in support for multiple language.
Before starting the post translation, make sure that you have enabled the language to your site. If that&amp;rsquo;s not the case, you can follow the section Add the language to the site from the guide How to Translate Site Data.
Creating the post Once you have your desired language added to your website, know you can translate posts to that language. We&amp;rsquo;re going to assume that you want to translate an existing post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Translate Site Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/translation/site-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 06:20:50 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/translation/site-data/</guid>
      <description>This theme has built-in support for multiple language.
Add the language to the site Adding the language to your site will translate the UI to that language (e.g. the buttons, the nav bars, etc.).
Get language code In order to translate your site, you will need the code from your language. The following table contains the supported languages algonside its codes:
Languages Code English en / none বাংলা bn Français fr Indonesian id Deutsch de Español es 简体中文 zh-cn / zh-tw हिन्दी hi Italiano it 日本語 jp 한국어 ko русский ru suomi fi Tiếng Việt vn Turkish tr Arabic (العربية) ar Português Europeu pt-pt Català ad Português Brasileiro pt-br Dutch nl For a complete list of the supported languages, please check the README file from the toha repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
